

Ayetolu S.

Android (Java|Kotlin),
Spring Boot Expert

General info

Work experience Location

5 years total Satellite Town, Nigeria

Time zone: UTC+1

Top technologies

Android	5+ years experience	1 2 3 4 5+
Java	5+ years experience	12345+
Firebase	5+ years experience	12345+
Kotlin	4 years experience	1 2 3 4 5+
RESTful APIs	4 years experience	1 2 3 4 5+

Technologies



Bio

Main areas of expertise

Android (Java|Kotlin), Spring Boot development.

Main tech stack

- Android (Java|Kotlin): > 4 years of professional experience
- Spring Boot: 2 years of professional experience

Jobs of interest

I'm interested in Android & Spring Boot Developer jobs, where I work with my main technologies.

Experience

Software Engineer Chamsmobile	04/2021 - now 1 year and 7 months
Android Developer ZuriChat	08/2021 - 11/2021 3 months
Software Engineer CHAMS PLC	07/2020 - 04/2021 9 months
Android Software Engineer Setnumd Technologies	02/2017 - 07/2020 3 years and 5 months

Education

National Open University of Nigeria	01/2018 - 01/2022
BSc, Mathematics and Computer Science	4 years

Languages

English Conversational